everythingglobe.com 2010-11-20

# Local classifieds - free online classifieds - sell your classifieds

**EverythingGlobe Privacy Policy**

EverythingGlobe is committed to safeguarding your online privacy. The following policy outlines how your personal information will be treated as you use our website.

EverythingGlobe may update this privacy policy from time to time, in order to take into account new laws and technology or to reflect changes in our operations. All personal information held by Sell Local will be governed by EverythingGlobe's most recent policy which will be displayed on this site.

**01\. What personal information do we collect?**  
EverythingGlobe primarily collects personal information from its users during the registration process. We collect and store users' names, email addresses, contact numbers and usernames and also other information including user's IP addresses and standard web log information. If a user contacts EverythingGlobe via email, a record of that correspondence may also be stored.

EverythingGlobe may place a cookie in the browser files of a user's computer. We use cookies to save information you give us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. This allows us to personalize the site to your taste and provide the best web experience possible to our users. We do not use cookies to track your movements on different web sites and do not exchange cookies with other entities.

**02\. How do we use your personal information?**  
EverythingGlobe uses the information collected to:

-Provide the products or services requested;  
-Communicate with our users;  
-Manage and enhance our services;  
-Resolve disputes and troubleshooting;  
-Measure interest in our services.

**03\. Disclosure  
**EverythingGlobe may provide your information to law enforcement to aid in their investigations of illegal or fraudulent postings. If EverythingGlobe sells part or all of its business, personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the purchaser.

**04\. How do we treat sensitive information?  
**"Sensitive Information" means information relating to a person's racial or ethnic origin, membership of political bodies, religion, membership of a trade union or professional or trade association, sexual preferences, criminal record and health.

EverythingGlobe may use and disclose sensitive information only for the purpose for which it was provided or a directly related secondary purpose or as allowed by law unless you have agreed otherwise.

**05\. Management and security of personal information  
**EverythingGlobe protects the personal information it holds from misuse, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure by various means including password access and secure servers. Only the administrators of EverythingGlobe and the user have access to that user's personal information. We recommend that users do not disclose their password to anyone.

**06\. Updating personal information  
**EverythingGlobe endeavours to ensure that the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up-to-date. Users can update their information after logging in. Alternatively, users can email ( support at EverythingGlobe dot com ) to advise of their information updates. Where personal information is no longer required by EverythingGlobe, it will be destroyed or de-identified.

**07\. Other information about your online privacy  
**Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online (for example in ads that you post or through email) that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online.

**08\. How to contact EverythingGlobe  
**If you have any enquiries or wish to provide feedback about this policy, please email ( support at EverythingGlobe dot com )
